http://www.gigavac.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Search form
Select the SearchProduct Spec SheetsSolid Models (STEP Files)WebsiteOnline Store
Search
HomeCatalogContactors, Switches & FusesGV Contactors 12 to 1000VdcGX Contactors 12 to 800VdcMX Contactors 12 to 100VdcHX Contactors 12 to 1500VdcPCB Mount DC Contactors 12 to 800VdcManual Disconnects 12 to 1000VdcP Series MiniTACTOR™ 12 to 1200VdcFusesHigh Voltage RelaysSingle Pole Single Throw, SPSTSingle Pole Double Throw, SPDTDouble Pole Double Throw, DPDTLatching – Bi-StableCompetitor Cross ReferenceSalesSales Offices & DistributorsPlace an OrderTerms & ConditionsSupportApplications AssistanceApplication NotesHigh Voltage RelaysPower ProductsAsk Sales Representative to CallAboutCompany OverviewPress ReleasesQuality & CertificationsCareersContactContact InfoSponsorship OpportunitiesMap & Driving Directions+1 805-684-8401gigavac@sensata.com
MenuHomeCatalogHigh Voltage RelaysHigh Voltage RelaysSingle Pole Single Throw, SPSTSingle Pole Double Throw, SPDTDouble Pole Double Throw, DPDTLatching – Bi-StableContactors, Switches & FusesContactors, Switches & FusesGV Contactors 12 to 800VdcGX Contactors 12 to 800VdcMX Contactors 12 to 100VdcHX Contactors 12 to 1500VdcPCB Mount DC Contactors 12 to 800VdcManual Disconnects 12 to 1000VdcP Series MiniTACTOR™ 12 to 1200VdcFusesCompetitor Cross ReferenceShopShopHigh Voltage RelaysHigh Voltage RelaysAmateur Radio RelayHigh Voltage RelayHigh Voltage Relay AccessoryHigh Voltage Relay CoilPower ProductsPower ProductsGV ContactorGX ContactorHX ContactorMX ContactorP Series ContactorManual SwitchPower Product AccessoryFusesSales Offices & DistributorsPlace an OrderSales TermsWarrantySupportApplications AssistanceApplication NotesApplication NotesHigh Voltage RelaysPower ProductsKeys to Selecting a Relay or ContactorAsk Sales Representative to CallAccessories & Complimentary ProductsAboutAboutCompany OverviewPress ReleasesQuality & CertificationsJob OpportunitiesContactContactContact InfoMap & Driving Directions
You are hereHome::Privacy Policy
Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, e-mail address, telephone number or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.
Our site may contain links to other sites, which are not managed or maintained by GIGAVAC. The inclusion of a link to another site from GIGAVAC does not imply any endorsement of that site's privacy policies, practices, or content and we will not share the information you give us with anyone other site.
Why does GIGAVAC ask for my information?
In order to send you application information, new product updates, company information or to provide you applications assistance by our field sales engineers you will need to provide some personal information.
What information does GIGAVAC collect?
We do not collect personal information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us from you on a voluntary basis.
How will GIGAVAC use the information I provide?
We will always explain the extent of its use at the time you are asked to provide personal information. If you do not want this information to be collected or used by us for these purposes, you can simply "opt out" by not providing the information.
Does GIGAVAC rent, sell, or trade my information?
No. The information you give us will not ever be supplied to anyone other than what was explained at the time you are asked to provide personal information.
Can I change the information I have given to GIGAVAC?
Yes. You can change or delete the information you have given us at anytime by sending us an e-mail at gigavac@sensata.com. We will take certain steps and may ask for additional information to prevent someone that is not authorized from changing your personal information.
What do I do if I have questions that aren't answered here?
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact:
Webmaster
WebMaster@GIGAVAC.com
